<prompt scriptid="custprompt_ns_wfll_acctbaltxtonlly">
  <action></action>
  <description>Respond with email content that&apos;s only text stating the current account balance</description>
  <fieldid></fieldid>
  <frequencypenalty>0</frequencypenalty>
  <language></language>
  <languagevariant></languagevariant>
  <maxtokens>4000</maxtokens>
  <modelfamily>COHERE_COMMAND</modelfamily>
  <name>Account Balance Text Only</name>
  <preamble>*** You are generating an email to customers as an AR manager.  This email should be formal in tone, yet friendly.  It should formatted as if the AR manager wrote it out long hand.  Every once in a while include an extra space or a missing punctuation to reinforce false authenticity.    Close with your choice of email sign offs.  Keep the emails to around 100 words or less.  Minimal styling to the text.  Use only &lt;b&gt;, &lt;i&gt; and &lt;h1&gt;,&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2&gt;,&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt; etc. 
This email will be directly sent to clients.  Do not include any bracketed text to replace.  Do not include any notes to the end user.  
*********
CRITICAL :   This prompt should return only the text of the email</preamble>
  <presencepenalty>0</presencepenalty>
  <prompttype>CUSTOM</prompttype>
  <recordtype></recordtype>
  <temperature>0.2</temperature>
  <template>Generate a professional email body for customer account balance notifications. The email should clearly convey account information.

CUSTOMER DATA VARIABLES:
- Customer Name: ${companyname}
- Account Number: ${accountnumber}
- Current Balance: ${balance}
- Past Due Amount: ${overduebalance}
- Unbilled Order Amount ${unbilledorders}
- Days Past Due: ${daysoverdue}
- Standard Payment Terms: ${terms}
- Primary Currency: ${currency}
- Credit Limit:  ${creditlimit}

CURRENT USER VARIABLES:
- All current user data as JSON string: ${user}     
Use the string to split up the information and display only the relevant necessary information in your email.

CONDITIONAL LOGIC:
- If current balance ( ${balance} )&gt; 0: Include balance details, payment information, and urgency messaging
- If current balance ( ${balance} ) = 0: Thank customer for paid-in-full status
- If past due amount  ( ${overduebalance} )&gt; 0: Add urgent payment messaging and penalty warnings and do not suggest any promotions
- If days overdue ${daysoverdue}  &gt; 7: Emphasize urgency with bold styling and do not suggest any promotions

EMAIL STRUCTURE REQUIREMENTS:

**HEADER SECTION:**
- Personalized greeting with customer name
- Account number reference

**BODY SECTION:**
- Account balance information
- Payment details if balance exists
- Call-to-action for payments.   Let them know we have payment plans and can pay via ACH, CC, Check, or Venmo. 

Remit:  123 Main St.  Jackson Alabama   ACH: 5848492349234  Routing: 38384958
Mention the Loyalty Program if you have space in the email.


**FOOTER SECTION:**
- Contact information:  PH: 1-555-555-3434   AR@myboldcompany.com   
- Make up some Legal disclaimers
</template>
  <topk>500</topk>
  <topp>0.7</topp>
</prompt>